He's L.A. Detective Mason Storm. Three hired assassins left him for
dead. And he's waited seven years to even the score.
Hard to Kill is a action, drama, crime film directed by Bruce Malmuth.
Mason Storm, a 'go it alone' cop, is gunned down at home.
The intruders kill his wife, and think they've
killed both Mason and his son too.
Mason is secretly taken to a hospital where he spends several years in a coma.
His son meanwhile is growing up thinking his father is dead.
When Mason wakes up, everyone is in danger - himself, his son, his best friend,
his nurse - but most of all those who arranged for his death
Mason Storm, played by Steven Seagal.
Andy Stewart, played by Kelly LeBrock.
Senator Vernon Trent, played by William Sadler.
Lt. Kevin O'Malley, played by Frederick Coffin.
Felicia Storm, played by Bonnie Burroughs.
Capt. Dan Hulland, played by Andrew Bloch.
Hard to Kill is a 1990 American vigilante action-thriller film directed by Bruce Malmuth, written by
Steven McKay, and starring Steven Seagal, Kelly LeBrock, William Sadler and Frederick Coffin.
Seagal's second film after Above the Law, he portrays Mason Storm, a detective who falls
into a coma after being shot during a home invasion that killed his wife.
Reawakening seven years later, Storm embarks on a journey to avenge the death of his wife, and expose
the corruption of Senator Vernon Trent, the man who ordered the murder of his family.
The film was released by Warner Bros.
on February 9, 1990, and grossed $75 million worldwide.
The film explores themes of martial arts, coma, training, cop, revenge.
The tone is emotional and intense.